// Data for Mathematical Operations game

// Defined as a global variable i.e. can be accessed from anywhere
// Complex combination of arrays and objects-for Easy, Medium ,Hard level for each game type: addition, subtraction ,multiplication and division
window.additionQuestionBank={"easy":[
  {
  "question":"1+3",
  "answer":"4",
  "options":["5","3","4","6"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4+8",
  "answer":"12",
  "options":["12","48","8","14"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4+7",
  "answer":"11",
  "options":["47","11","12","13"]
  },
  {
  "question":"7+9",
  "answer":"16",
  "options":["15","14","63","16"]
  },
  {
  "question":"7+5",
  "answer":"12",
  "options":["75","11","12","13"]
  },
  {
  "question":"2+8",
  "answer":"10",
  "options":["12","10","14","16"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4+1",
  "answer":"5",
  "options":["5","3","4","6"]
  },
  {
  "question":"0+9",
  "answer":"9",
  "options":["5","3","9","0"]
  },
  {
  "question":"9+12",
  "answer":"21",
  "options":["21","23","22","31"]
  },
  {
  "question":"41+5",
  "answer":"46",
  "options":["45","43","49","46"]
  }
  ],
  "medium":[
  {
  "question":"14+23",
  "answer":"37",
  "options":["27","37","47","36"]
  },
  {
  "question":"32+8",
  "answer":"40",
  "options":["40","39","41","36"]
  },
  {
  "question":"44+17",
  "answer":"61",
  "options":["51","61","71","63"]
  },
  {
  "question":"17+29",
  "answer":"46",
  "options":["45","36","56","46"]
  },
  {
  "question":"71+5",
  "answer":"76",
  "options":["75","78","76","86"]
  },
  {
  "question":"21+38",
  "answer":"59",
  "options":["59","69","49","56"]
  },
  {
  "question":"497+103",
  "answer":"600",
  "options":["501","500","503","600"]
  },
  {
  "question":"331+129",
  "answer":"460",
  "options":["560","390","460","650"]
  },
  {
  "question":"102+103",
  "answer":"205",
  "options":["204","205","305","304"]
  },
  {
  "question":"391+129",
  "answer":"520",
  "options":["520","320","420","620"]
  }
  ],
  "hard":[
  {
  "question":"125+576",
  "answer":"701",
  "options":["801","701","601","699"]
  },
  {
  "question":"417+312",
  "answer":"729",
  "options":["729","629","749","739"]
  },
  {
  "question":"351+552",
  "answer":"903",
  "options":["902","903","804","901"]
  },
  {
  "question":"671+219",
  "answer":"890",
  "options":["891","790","990","890"]
  },
  {
  "question":"472+275",
  "answer":"747",
  "options":["547","647","747","749"]
  },
  {
  "question":"298+687",
  "answer":"985",
  "options":["1005","995","985","895"]
  },
  {
  "question":"474+159",
  "answer":"633",
  "options":["733","633","533","623"]
  },
  {
  "question":"378+97",
  "answer":"475",
  "options":["575","375","475","675"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4774+1759",
  "answer":"6553",
  "options":["6733","6433","6533","6233"]
  },
  {
  "question":"3178+972",
  "answer":"4150",
  "options":["4050","4150","3950","4250"]
  }
]};
window.subtractionQuestionBank={"easy":[
    {
    "question":"3-1",
    "answer":"2",
    "options":["3","2","4","5"]
    },
    {
    "question":"8-4",
    "answer":"4",
    "options":["6","3","4","5"]
    },
    {
    "question":"7-2",
    "answer":"5",
    "options":["5","6","9","4"]
    },
    {
    "question":"9-7",
    "answer":"2",
    "options":["1","3","4","2"]
    },
    {
    "question":"10-3",
    "answer":"7",
    "options":["7","8","13","6"]
    },
    {
    "question":"8-7",
    "answer":"1",
    "options":["0","1","2","-1"]
    },
    {
    "question":"4-0",
    "answer":"4",
    "options":["1","3","4","2"]
    },
    {
    "question":"24-9",
    "answer":"15",
    "options":["14","13","15","17"]
    },
    {
    "question":"14-6",
    "answer":"8",
    "options":["7","4","9","8"]
    },
    {
    "question":"36-12",
    "answer":"24",
    "options":["25","23","21","24"]
    }
    ],
    "medium":[
    {
    "question":"49-13",
    "answer":"36",
    "options":["35","34","39","36"]
    },
    {
    "question":"87-47",
    "answer":"40",
    "options":["39","40","41","38"]
    },
    {
    "question":"72-26",
    "answer":"46",
    "options":["56","46","49","54"]
    },
    {
    "question":"91-73",
    "answer":"18",
    "options":["28","38","18","22"]
    },
    {
    "question":"100-34",
    "answer":"66",
    "options":["57","56","46","66"]
    },
    {
    "question":"89-45",
    "answer":"44",
    "options":["42","47","34","44"]
    },
    {
    "question":"109-56",
    "answer":"53",
    "options":["51","53","46","43"]
    },
    {
    "question":"124-93",
    "answer":"31",
    "options":["31","41","54","21"]
    },
    {
    "question":"245-47",
    "answer":"98",
    "options":["99","78","88","98"]
    },
    {
    "question":"891-145",
    "answer":"746",
    "options":["646","746","576","686"]
    }
    ],
    "hard":[
    {
    "question":"4887-13",
    "answer":"4874",
    "options":["4884","4874","4754","4864"]
    },
    {
    "question":"1002-123",
    "answer":"879",
    "options":["779","979","879","889"]
    },
    {
    "question":"2145-586",
    "answer":"1559",
    "options":["1157","1559","1459","1659"]
    },
    {
    "question":"4134-1024",
    "answer":"3110",
    "options":["3210","4110","3110","2910"]
    },
    {
    "question":"987-456",
    "answer":"531",
    "options":["531","561","461","431"]
    },
    {
    "question":"7849-1649",
    "answer":"6200",
    "options":["5200","5800","6000","6200"]
    },
    {
    "question":"9658-7895",
    "answer":"1763",
    "options":["1563","1263","563","1763"]
    },
    {
    "question":"2974-913",
    "answer":"2061",
    "options":["2061","2014","2041","2141"]
    },
    {
    "question":"7596-258",
    "answer":"7338",
    "options":["7438","7348","7338","7548"]
    },
    {
    "question":"5896-3597",
    "answer":"2299",
    "options":["2299","2439","2399","2300"]
    }
]};
window.multiplicationQuestionBank={"easy":[
  {
  "question":"1*3",
  "answer":"3",
  "options":["5","3","4","6"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4*8",
  "answer":"32",
  "options":["12","48","32","24"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4*7",
  "answer":"28",
  "options":["47","35","21","28"]
  },
  {
  "question":"7*9",
  "answer":"63",
  "options":["65","14","63","56"]
  },
  {
  "question":"7*5",
  "answer":"35",
  "options":["75","37","12","35"]
  },
  {
  "question":"2*8",
  "answer":"16",
  "options":["12","8","24","16"]
  },
  {
  "question":"4*1",
  "answer":"4",
  "options":["4","8","41","14"]
  },
  {
  "question":"0*9",
  "answer":"0",
  "options":["0","1","9","18"]
  },
  {
  "question":"12*3",
  "answer":"36",
  "options":["24","36","46","32"]
  },
  {
  "question":"14*3",
  "answer":"42",
  "options":["32","42","22","56"]
  }
  ],
  "medium":[
  {
  "question":"14*23",
  "answer":"322",
  "options":["322","372","332","342"]
  },
  {
  "question":"32*8",
  "answer":"256",
  "options":["296","256","296","236"]
  },
  {
  "question":"44*17",
  "answer":"748",
  "options":["648","768","748","688"]
  },
  {
  "question":"17*29",
  "answer":"493",
  "options":["493","446","456","483"]
  },
  {
  "question":"71*5",
  "answer":"355",
  "options":["335","375","365","355"]
  },
  {
  "question":"21*38",
  "answer":"798",
  "options":["598","698","798","568"]
  },
  {
  "question":"49*93",
  "answer":"4557",
  "options":["4447","4557","4667","4747"]
  },
  {
  "question":"33*101",
  "answer":"3333",
  "options":["3324","3223","3323","3333"]
  },
  {
  "question":"102*103",
  "answer":"10506",
  "options":["10605","10116","10406","10506"]
  },
  {
  "question":"133*11",
  "answer":"1463",
  "options":["1663","1563","1443","1463"]
  }
  ],
  "hard":[
  {
  "question":"110*110",
  "answer":"12100",
  "options":["11100","12210","12100","22100"]
  },
  {
  "question":"114*115",
  "answer":"13110",
  "options":["13210","13110","13310","21110"]
  },
  {
  "question":"320*150",
  "answer":"48000",
  "options":["48000","49000","46000","47000"]
  },
  {
  "question":"170*25",
  "answer":"4250",
  "options":["4350","4450","5400","4250"]
  },
  {
  "question":"278*32",
  "answer":"8896",
  "options":["8786","8996","8896","7896"]
  },
  {
  "question":"300*64",
  "answer":"19200",
  "options":["19200","21200","20200","18200"]
  },
  {
  "question":"185*165",
  "answer":"30525",
  "options":["30455","30255","30425","30525"]
  },
  {
  "question":"95*400",
  "answer":"38000",
  "options":["37000","36000","38000","36500"]
  },
  {
  "question":"654*321",
  "answer":"209934",
  "options":["219933","219934","219934","209934"]
  },
  {
  "question":"256*128",
  "answer":"32768",
  "options":["34668","32468","32768","36888"]
  }
]};
window.divisionQuestionBank={"easy":[
  {
  "question":"2/1",
  "answer":"2",
  "options":["3","2","4","1"]
  },
  {
  "question":"8/4",
  "answer":"2",
  "options":["6","3","4","2"]
  },
  {
  "question":"14/2",
  "answer":"7",
  "options":["5","7","9","4"]
  },
  {
  "question":"9/3",
  "answer":"3",
  "options":["1","3","4","2"]
  },
  {
  "question":"21/3",
  "answer":"7",
  "options":["7","8","9","6"]
  },
  {
  "question":"18/6",
  "answer":"3",
  "options":["0","1","2","3"]
  },
  {
  "question":"0/5",
  "answer":"0",
  "options":["1","3","4","0"]
  },
  {
  "question":"63/3",
  "answer":"21",
  "options":["14","21","15","22"]
  },
  {
  "question":"56/7",
  "answer":"8",
  "options":["7","4","9","8"]
  },
  {
  "question":"36/4",
  "answer":"9",
  "options":["6","7","9","8"]
  }
  ],
  "medium":[
  {
  "question":"49/7",
  "answer":"7",
  "options":["6","7","9","8"]
  },
  {
  "question":"81/3",
  "answer":"27",
  "options":["26","25","27","31"]
  },
  {
  "question":"256/8",
  "answer":"32",
  "options":["32","42","36","64"]
  },
  {
  "question":"363/121",
  "answer":"3",
  "options":["4","2","3","6"]
  },
  {
  "question":"100/25",
  "answer":"4",
  "options":["6","4","8","5"]
  },
  {
  "question":"74/2",
  "answer":"37",
  "options":["36","37","33","47"]
  },
  {
  "question":"343/7",
  "answer":"49",
  "options":["59","69","49","89"]
  },
  {
  "question":"625/25",
  "answer":"25",
  "options":["30","35","50","25"]
  },
  {
  "question":"144/6",
  "answer":"24",
  "options":["24","26","34","14"]
  },
  {
  "question":"512/64",
  "answer":"8",
  "options":["7","6","8","9"]
  }
  ],
  "hard":[
  {
  "question":"3354/13",
  "answer":"258",
  "options":["248","268","258","288"]
  },
  {
  "question":"7995/123",
  "answer":"65",
  "options":["85","75","95","65"]
  },
  {
  "question":"14650/586",
  "answer":"25",
  "options":["55","35","45","25"]
  },
  {
  "question":"66560/1040",
  "answer":"64",
  "options":["34","64","84","44"]
  },
  {
  "question":"15900/1325",
  "answer":"12",
  "options":["22","32","42","12"]
  },
  {
  "question":"31000/1240",
  "answer":"25",
  "options":["45","35","25","75"]
  },
  {
  "question":"9600/240",
  "answer":"40",
  "options":["80","160","40","64"]
  },
  {
  "question":"43740/972",
  "answer":"45",
  "options":["55","85","65","45"]
  },
  {
  "question":"16512/64",
  "answer":"258",
  "options":["248","268","258","358"]
  },
  {
  "question":"148200/1235",
  "answer":"120",
  "options":["140","160","120","180"]
  }
]};
